<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cpp primer on 颢阳's Blog</title><link>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/tags/cpp-primer/</link><description>Recent content in cpp primer on 颢阳's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>颢阳</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 10:08:12 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.peterchen.xyz/tags/cpp-primer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cpp Primer Chapter 2</title><link>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/reads/cpp-primer-ch2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 10:08:12 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/reads/cpp-primer-ch2/</guid><description>C++ language specifics Python check types at run time, whereas C++ is statically typed language — type-check is done at compile time. As a consequence, the compiler must know the type of every name used in the program.
Primitive Buit-in Types C++ defines a set of primitive types that include the arithmetic types and a special type named void. The arithmetic types represent characters, integers, boolean values, and floating-point numbers. The void type has no associated values and can be used in only a few circumstances, most commonly as the return type for functions that do not return a value.</description></item><item><title>Cpp Primer Chapter 1</title><link>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/reads/cpp-primer-ch1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 21:36:54 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/reads/cpp-primer-ch1/</guid><description>Starting from today, I will read and write notes for C++ primer. I will only write notes that I think that is important, so not all the contents will be covered.
Design a bookstore Our store keeps a file of transactions, each of which records the sale of one or more copies of a single book. Each transaction contains three data elements:
0-201-70353-X 4 24.99 The first element is an ISBN (International Standard Book Number, a unique book identifier), the second is the number of copies sold, and the last is the price at which each of these copies was sold.</description></item></channel></rss>