<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>thoughts on 颢阳's Blog</title><link>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/categories/thoughts/</link><description>Recent content in thoughts on 颢阳's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>颢阳</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 20:25:59 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.peterchen.xyz/categories/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emailing as a Course</title><link>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/email-as-a-course/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 20:25:59 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/email-as-a-course/</guid><description>So it&amp;rsquo;s my last semester of work in NYU, and I chose to take an independent study class with Prof. Yury Dvorkin. He is very busy on his research works, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t really expect too much from this course (it&amp;rsquo;s only 1.5 credit), so we agreed on meeting once per two weeks.
Send everything using email isn&amp;rsquo;t bad at all, it&amp;rsquo;s even more efficient In order to provide some help in case he was busy, he delegated an PhD student named Samrat supervised by him.</description></item><item><title>2021 H1b Lottery</title><link>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/2021-h1b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 23:17:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/2021-h1b/</guid><description>今天是抽签放出结果的第一个工作日，我们公司用的是Fragomen律所负责申请工作签证。美国的工作签证简称h1b visa, 是给美国的外来人口工作的一种</description></item><item><title>关闭朋友圈</title><link>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/%E5%85%B3%E9%97%AD%E6%9C%8B%E5%8F%8B%E5%9C%88/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 19:34:06 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/%E5%85%B3%E9%97%AD%E6%9C%8B%E5%8F%8B%E5%9C%88/</guid><description>关闭朋友圈大概有一周了，不知道是不是我的心理作用，感觉比之前过的更加充实了。 什么时间，为什么关 大概是一个礼拜之前关的。原因其实没有什么特别的</description></item><item><title>How to Talk</title><link>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/how-to-talk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 13:10:37 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/how-to-talk/</guid><description>After I got my job offer, I have done multiple mock interviews with different people. I guess I miss the feeling of being interviewed, as well as interviewing others. Throughout the interview experiences with others, I have somehow figured out a way of talking with people.
People you know I love talking with people I know beforehand. It&amp;rsquo;s ususally a great experience to talk with them, since you know them well and you can avoid saying something stupid but you are unaware of.</description></item><item><title>Why DoorDash Cannot Deliver Your Order Properly</title><link>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/why-doordash-cannot-deliver-your-order-properly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 19:45:47 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/why-doordash-cannot-deliver-your-order-properly/</guid><description>So I have requested a food delivery from DoorDash, and it happened that my food still hadn&amp;rsquo;t been picked up yet. I opened my DoorDash app at 12:30 pm today, and it&amp;rsquo;s still being prepared until now at 7:50 pm. During the approximately 8 hours wait, I have tried to reach out to them three times, and each agent responded to me with a predefined message: &amp;ldquo;We are sorry for the delay &amp;hellip; We will assign a new dasher for you &amp;hellip; We will refund you the money amount XXX&amp;rdquo;, etc.</description></item><item><title>What Does It Mean When You Turn 25</title><link>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/what-does-it-mean-when-you-turn-25/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 09:07:56 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peterchen.xyz/posts/what-does-it-mean-when-you-turn-25/</guid><description>I always wonder why people care so much about their ages &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s unchangeable and unstoppable, which seems really meaningless to talk about it. I have been thinking about it for a really long time, until recently I gradually understand it.
Time is defined by people. I reminisce at the age of me going primary school, when I thought about growing up was just graduating from here, and not knowing that there are middle school, high school and university waiting for me.</description></item></channel></rss>